Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 8 and District 8 Locals, 1936-1957 UE.4.1.8
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 8, 1.
  - District 8 William Sentner Outgoing Correspondence, March 19 - April 21, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Sentner to William Mauseth Regarding Negotiations and Minneapolis Moline, March 1942; 7.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Servel Organization, March 1942; 8.
    - Sentner to Charles LaValley Regarding Minneapolis Moline Organization and American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, April 2, 1942; 9.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding U.S. Cartridge Organization, April 2, 1942; 10.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Des Moines Small Arms Organization, April 2, 1942; 11.
    - Sentner to Gilbert Prather Regarding Staff Members, April 6, 1942; 12.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members and Des Moines Organization, April 9, 1942; 13.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, April 14, 1942; 14.
    - Sentner to James Payne Regarding Dues, April 15, 1942; 15.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Evansville Organization, April 15, 1942; 16.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Rockford Organization, April 15, 1942; 17.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Tool and Dye Makers Council, April 16, 1942; 18.
    - Sentner to Lyle Dowling Regarding Government Office, April 20, 1942; 19.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, April 21, 1942; 20.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Servel Organization and Staff Members, April 21, 1942; 21.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Cairo Edison and Employment, April 21, 1942; 22.
    - Sentner to S. F. Larchar Regarding Cairo Edison and Employment, April 21, 1942; 23.
    - Sentner to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Production Conference, April 21, 1942; 24.
  - District 8 William Sentner Outgoing Correspondence, April 29 - June 10, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Sentner to Lyle Dowling Regarding Post War Production, April 29, 1942; 1.
    - Sentner to James Matles Regarding Office of Production Managment and Staff Members, April 1942; 2.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Productivity, April 1942; 3.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Organization, Amertorp and United Steelworkers of America Inter-union Rivalry, May 4, 1942; 4.
    - Sentner to Julius Emspak Regarding Education Department, May 11, 1942; 5.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Chicago Organization, May 12, 1942; 6.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members and U.S. Cartridge Organization, May 14, 1942; 7.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding U.S. Cartridge Organization and Staff Members, May 20, 1942; 8.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Dues, Finances and General Executive Board, May 23, 1942; 9.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Emerson Staff Members, May 23, 1942; 10.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Cairo Edison Organization and Inter-union Rivalry, May 27, 1942; 11.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding General Executive Board, May 28, 1942; 12.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Evansville Organization and Amalgamation of Locals 813 and 1002, June 5, 1942; 13.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Finances and Cairo Organization, June 9, 1942; 14.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding District Executive Board, June 9, 1942; 15.
    - Sentner to Albert Smith Regarding Staff Members, June 9, 1942; 16.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Cairo Organization and Evansville, June 10, 1942; 17.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Washington Office, June 10, 1942; 18.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Local 1121 and Evansville Sunbeam Organization, June 10, 1942; 19.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 10, 1942; 20.
  - District 8 William Sentner Outgoing Correspondence, June 15 - August 24, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Sentner to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, June 15, 1942; 1.
    - Sentner to James Matles Regarding Organization and Cairo, June 23, 1942; 2.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 23, 1942; 3.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Ken Ran Organization, June 30, 1942; 4.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, July 1, 1942; 5.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding War Labor Board and U.S. Cartridge, July 7, 1942; 6.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding U.S. Cartridge Organization, July 7, 1942; 7.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Evansville Organization, July 7, 1942; 8.
    - Sentner Regarding Staff Finances, July 13, 1942; 9.
    - Sentner to James Payne Regarding Owensboro Organization, July 21, 1942; 10.
    - Sentner to Charles Rivers Regarding Conference, July 21, 1942; 11.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Cairo Organization and Inter-union Rivalry, July 21, 1942; 12.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Cairo Edison Organization and Inter-union Rivalry, July 22, 1942; 13.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Finances, July 24, 1942; 14.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, July 24, 1942; 15.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Ordinance Workers Conference, July 29, 1942; 16.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, August 3, 1942; 17.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members and Cairo, August 13, 1942; 18.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding GE Kokomo Organization and Inter-union Rivalry, August 24, 1942; 19.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Organization and Cairo, August 24, 1942; 20.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers, August 26, 1942; 21.
  - District 8 William Sentner Outgoing Correspondence, August 26 - June 10, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Sentner to James Matles Regarding U.S. Cartridge Organization, August 26, 1942; 1.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, August 26, 1942; 2.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Cairo Edison Organization, August 26, 1942; 3.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding U.S. Cartridge Organization and Inter-union Rivalry, August 28, 1942; 4.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding U.S. Cartridge Organization and Staff Members, August 28, 1942; 5.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Cairo Edison Organization, August 31, 1942; 6.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, September 16, 1942; 7.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, September 17, 1942; 8.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Cairo Organization and Inter-union Rivalry, September 23, 1942; 9.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, September 29, 1942; 10.
    - Sentner to Julius Emspak Regarding Education Department, May 11, 1942; 11.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Chicago Organization, May 12, 1942; 12.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members and U.S. Cartridge Organization, May 14, 1942; 13.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding U.S. Cartridge Organization, Women and Staff Members, May 20, 1942; 14.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Dues, Finances and General Executive Board Organization, May 23, 1942; 15.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Emerson and Staff Members, May 23, 1942; 16.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Cairo Edison Organization and Inter-union Rivalry, May 27, 1942; 17.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding General Executive Board, May 28, 1942; 18.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Evansville Organization and Amalgamation of Locals 813 and 1002, June 5, 1942; 19.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Finances and Cairo Organization, June 9, 1942; 20.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding District Executive Board, June 9, 1942; 21.
    - Sentner to Albert Smith Regarding Staff Members, June 9, 1942; 22.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Cairo Organization and Evansville, June 10, 1942; 23.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Local 112 and Sunbeam Organization, June 10, 1942; 24.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Washington Office, June 10, 1942; 25.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 10, 1942; 26.
  - District 8 William Sentner Outgoing Correspondence, October 20 - December 9, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Sentner to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, October 20, 1942; 1.
    - Sentner to Grant Oaks Regarding Organization, Collins Radio, ABC Washing Machines, and Farm Equipment Workers Inter-union Rivalry, October 20, 1942; 2.
    - Sentner to Lyle Dowling Regarding Political Action, October 26, 1942; 3.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, October 28, 1942; 4.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, October 28, 1942; 5.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Edison Organization, Cairo, and AFL Inter-union Rivalry, October 30, 1942; 6.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members and U.S. Cartridge Organization, November 2, 1942; 7.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, November 2, 1942; 8.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, November 20, 1942; 9.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding District 10, Staff Members and FE Inter-union Rivalry, November 24, 1942; 10.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members and Women, November 23, 1942; 11.
    - Sentner to Jerry Fields Regarding FE, Organization and ABC Washing Machines, November 24, 1942; 12.
    - Sentner to Gus Townsen Regarding Job Evaluation, Emerson and Sunbeam Century, November 27, 1942; 13.
    - Sentner to Dowling Regarding Chicago Emergency, Conference and Wages, December 1, 1942; 14.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, December 2, 1942; 15.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Holidays, Decembr 4, 1942; 16.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 7, 1942; 17.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, December 9, 1942; 18.
  - District 8 William Sentner Outgoing Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Sentner to A. N. Townsen Regarding Wages and Profits, December 29, 1942; 1.
    - Sentner to James Matles Regarding Wages and Staff Members, December 29, 1942; 2.
    - Sentner to Townsen Regarding Wages, December 29, 1942; 3.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, December 29, 1942; 4.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members and New York Conference, December 31, 1942; 5.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Organization, U.S. Cartridge and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, December 31, 1942; 6.
    - Sentner to Dwight Green Regarding Cairo Edison Organization and American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, 1942; 7.
    - Sentner to J. V. Forestal Regarding Cairo Edison Organization and AFL Inter-union Rivalry, 1942; 8.
    - Sentner to Thomas Gaukel Regarding Manpower, African Americans and Women, January 3, 1943; 9.
    - Sentner to Edward McDonald Regarding War Manpower Commission, January 3, 1943; 10.
    - Sentner to Fowler Harper Regarding War Manpower Commission, January 4, 1943; 11.
    - Sentner to Walter Frisbee Regarding Evansville War Manpower Commission, January 22, 1943; 12.
    - Sentner to Julius Emspak Regarding Political Action and Wages, January 22, 1943; 13.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Political Action and Wages, January 22, 1943; 14.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Negotiations and Decca, January 22, 1943; 15.
    - Sentner to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding District 8 Visit, February 2, 1943; 16.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Cannon Electric Organization, February 3, 1943; 17.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, February 3, 1943; 18.
    - Sentner to Local 1110 President Regarding Southern Illinois and Indiana, February 8, 1943; 19.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Evansville Organization and Staff Members, February 12, 1943; 20.
  - District 8 William Sentner Outgoing Correspondence, February 12 - March 5, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Sentner to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, February 12, 1943; 1.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, February 12, 1943; 2.
    - Sentner to Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, February 12, 1943; 3.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding War Production Board, February 16, 1943; 4.
    - Sentner to E. B. Epping Regarding War Production Board and Arkansas, February 16, 1943; 5.
    - Sentner to Joe Hood Regarding Staff Members, February 16, 1943; 6.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, February 16, 1943; 7.
    - Sentner to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding CIO, February 16, 1943; 8.
    - Sentner to Fitzgerald Regarding War Labor Board and United Auto Workers, February 16, 1943; 9.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding U.S. Cartridge Negotiation, February 16, 1943; 10.
    - Sentner to Fitzgerald Regarding Fitzgerald Visit, February 17, 1943; 11.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Organization and White Collar Workers, February 19, 1943; 12.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Finances and Locals 1102, 1004, and 1108, February 19, 1943; 13.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, February 22, 1943; 14.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, February 22, 1943; 15.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, February 22, 1943; 16.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding War Production Board, February 27, 1943; 17.
    - Sentner to Stella Abrams Regarding Address, March 5, 1943; 18.
    - Sentner to Fitzgerald Regarding War Labor Board and CIO Conference, March 5, 1943; 19.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Finances and U.S. Cartridge Organization, March 5, 1943; 20.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, March 5, 1943; 21.
  - District 8 William Sentner Outgoing Correspondence, March 16 - May 18, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Sentner to James Matles Regarding Bechler Steel Products Organization, March 16, 1943; 1.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Servel Organization, April 4, 1943; 2.
    - Sentner to William McClellan Regarding St. Louis Post War Planning, April 16, 1943; 3.
    - Sentner to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding War Labor Board and Political Action, April 12, 1943; 4.
    - Sentner to James Matles Regarding Servel Organization, April 15, 1943; 5.
    - Sentner to Neil Brant Regarding Wages and Political Action, April 28, 1943; 6.
    - Sentner to Julius Emspak Regarding UE News, April 28, 1943; 7.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding American Arbitration Association, April 28, 1943; 8.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding GE Contracts and Wages, April 29, 1943; 9.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding U.S. Cartridge Organization, May 4, 1943; 10.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding CIO, May 3, 1943; 11.
    - Sentner to John Brophy Regarding War Labor Board and Wages, May 10, 1943; 12.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Kansas City Organization, May 10, 1943; 13.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding United Auto Workers, May 12, 1943; 14.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Organization, May 17, 1943; 15.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Finances, May 18, 1943; 16.
  - District 8 William Sentner Outgoing Correspondence, June 9 - July 30, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Sentner to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 9, 1943; 1.
    - Sentner to Julius Emspak Regarding Disbanding and Local 820, June 10, 1943; 2.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Lukas Harold Organization, June 18, 1943; 3.
    - Sentner to E. F. Stevens Regarding Negotiations, Decca Records and War Labor Board, June 24, 1943; 4.
    - Sentner to Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, June 24, 1943; 5.
    - Sentner to Neil Brant Regarding War Labor Board, July 1, 1943; 6.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Lukas Harold Organization, undated; 7.
    - Sentner to Ernest DeMaio Regarding Staff Members, July 2, 1943; 8.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Contracts and Westinghouse, July 2, 1943; 9.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, July 6, 1943; 10.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, July 7, 1943; 11.
    - Sentner to Russ Nixon Regarding War Manpower Commission, July 7, 1943; 12.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Local 1104 Per Capita, July 7, 1943; 13.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, July 21, 1943; 14.
    - Sentner to Sidney Hillman Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations Political Action Committee and Political Action, July 14, 1943; 15.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Contracts and Westinghouse Maytag, July 14, 1943; 16.
    - Sentner to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding CIO, July 14, 1943; 17.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, July 15, 1943; 18.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Indianapolis CIO, July 15, 1943; 19.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, July 27, 1943; 20-21.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, July 30, 1943; 22.
  - District 8 William Sentner Outgoing Correspondence, August 2 - October 13, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Sentner to James Matles Regarding CIO and Political Action, August 2, 1943; 1.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, August 9, 1943; 2.
    - Sentner to Thomas Quinn Regarding Productivity, August 16, 1943; 3.
    - Sentner to Russ Nixon Regarding Inflation and Political Action, August 19, 1943; 4.
    - Sentner to Nixon Regarding War Labor Board and Political Action, August 20, 1943; 5.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding UE Convention, August 23, 1943; 6.
    - Sentner to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding CIO and Political Action Committee, August 28, 1943; 7.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, September 3, 1943; 8.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Staff Members and Texas Organization, September 6, 1943; 9.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding Western Electric Organization and Inter-union Rivalry, September 7, 1943; 10.
    - Sentner to Matles Regarding War Labor Board, Western Electric, Dues, Check-off and Wages, September 7, 1943; 11.
    - Sentner to Lou Kimmel Regarding Wendall Wilke, September 22, 1943; 12.
    - Sentner to Julius Emspak Regarding Mailing List, October 2, 1943; 13.
    - Sentner to Fitzgerald Regarding Contracts, October 8, 1943; 14.
    - Sentner to John Nordman Regarding Staff Members, October 8, 1943; 15.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Finances and Staff Members, October 9, 1943; 16.
    - Sentner to Otto Maschaff Regarding Staff Members and Local 825, October 9, 1943; 17.
    - Sentner to David Scribner Regarding Staff Members, October 9, 1943; 18.
    - Sentner to Martin Hourihan Regarding Staff Members, October 11, 1943; 19.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 12, 1943; 20.
    - Sentner to Fitzgerald Regarding CIO PAC, October 12, 1943; 21.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, October 13, 1943; 22.
  - District 8 William Sentner Outgoing Correspondence, October 19 - November 30, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Sentner to A. F. Kojetinsky Regarding War Labor Board and United Steelworkers of America Inter-union Rivalry, October 19, 1943; 1.
    - Sentner to Ray Klausner Regarding Local 1009 Organization, October 19, 1943; 2.
    - Sentner to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, October 19, 1943; 3.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Officers and District 8, October 19, 1943; 4.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Chicago Political Action Committee Conference, October 19, 1943; 5.
    - Sentner to David Scribner Regarding Evansville Huntington Organization, October 19, 1943; 6.
    - Sentner to Sidney Hillman Regarding CIO Political Action Committee, October 19, 1943; 7.
    - Sentner to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding CIO, October 19, 1943; 8.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Sangamo Meter Organization and USWA Inter-union Rivalry, October 20, 1943; 9.
    - Sentner to John Dougherty Regarding Sangamo Meter Organization and USWA Inter-union Rivalry, October 20, 1943; 10.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Staff Meeting; Organization; Inter-union Rivalry; Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers and USWA; CIO PAC; and American Soviet Friendship Conference, October 26, 1943; 11.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding USWA, October 26, 1943; 12.
    - Sentner to Jack Tanner Regarding WWII Engineering Union of England, October 26, 1943; 13.
    - Sentner to All District 8 Locals Regarding Engineering Union of England, USSR and Confederation of Latin American Workers, October 27, 1943; 14.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, November 15, 1943; 15.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, November 30, 1943; 16.
  - District 8 William Sentner Outgoing Correspondence, December 1, 1943 - February 15, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Sentner to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Conscriptions, December 1, 1943; 1.
    - Sentner to Julius Emspak Regarding General Executive Board and Ladies Auxiliary, December 3, 1943; 2.
    - Sentner to All Union Secretaries Regarding Finances, December 4, 1943; 3.
    - Sentner to Fitzgerald Regarding Constitution, Local 803 and Local 813, December 21, 1943; 4.
    - Sentner to David Scribner Regarding Convention Proceedings, December 28, 1943; 5.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, December 28, 1943; 6-7.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Bendix and Singer Organization, December 31, 1943; 8.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Kansas City Organization, December 31, 1943; 9.
    - Sentner to Fitzgerald Regarding Fitzgerald Visit with Schedule, January 4, 1944; 10.
    - Sentner to Ernest DeMaio Regarding Staff Members, January 10, 1944; 11.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding California, January 17, 1944; 12.
    - Sentner to Martin Hourihan Regarding California Trip, January 17, 1944; 13.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Military Personnel, January 20, 1944; 14.
    - Sentner to Ed Matthews Regarding Westinghouse and Incentive Pay, January 21, 1944; 15.
    - Sentner to Ed Warren Regarding War Labor Board, February 7, 1944; 16.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding California and Staff Members, February 7, 1944; 17.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Finances and Local 1421, February 7, 1944; 18.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Universal Equipment Organization and American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, February 15, 1944; 19.
  - District 8 William Sentner Outgoing Correspondence, February 17 - April 7, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Sentner to Morris Muster Regarding Atlas Truck and United Furniture Workers, February 17, 1944; 1.
    - Sentner to Julius Emspak Regarding Dues and Check-off, February 17, 1944; 2.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, February 17, 1944; 3.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding War Manpower Commission, February 19, 1944; 4.
    - Sentner to John Gojack Regarding St. Joe Visit, February 21, 1944; 5.
    - Sentner to Victor Decavitch Regarding Cleveland Visit, February 21, 1944; 6.
    - Sentner to Fitzgerald Regarding Post War Planning, February 21, 1944; 7.
    - Sentner to Russ Nixon Regarding Fascism and Unemployment, February 21, 1944; 8.
    - Sentner to Tom Wright Regarding UE News and Radio Conference, March 3, 1944; 9.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, March 8, 1944; 10.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Staff Members and Local 1104 Per Capita, March 8, 1944; 11.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, March 8, 1944; 12.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Supplies, March 28, 1944; 13.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding UE Constitution, March 29, 1944; 14.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Evansville Organization, March 29, 1944; 15.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, March 30, 1944; 16.
    - Sentner to Gus Townsen Regarding Military Severence Pay, March 31, 1944; 17.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Finances and Local 1421, April 3, 1944; 18.
    - Sentner to Carl Brant Regarding Finances and Local 1421, April 3, 1944; 19.
    - Sentner to Emspak Regarding Finances and Staff Members, April 3, 1944; 20.
    - Sentner to David Scribner Regarding Staff Members, April 5, 1944; 21.
    - Sentner to Fitzgerald Regarding United Motors Service Organization and United Auto Workers, April 7, 1944; 22.
  - District 8 William Sentner Outgoing Correspondence, April 17 - June 30, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Sentner to Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, April 17, 1944; 1.
    - Sentner to Julius Emspak Regarding Financial Report, April 17, 1944; 2.
    - Sentner to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding United Auto Workers and United Motor Organization, April 18, 1944; 3.